Hey guys, welcome back to One Momini
Vlog. My
brother-in-law got married and was invited to my sister Saurik's
family's house.
And Aunty cooked many dishes for us
.  Prasad is also busy
.  They
also cooked my favorite chicken biryani.
The taste is very good.  I didn't expect Aunty to
cook so well
.  Then Saurik sir
started to show respect.  Everything is
nearby and being served.  We all
sat down and finished lunch.
We felt very happy that so many dishes were cooked for us in such a short time
.  In the afternoon, Saurik sir
took me shopping.  They
even gave clothes to the newlyweds as a way to buy some for my sister.  They also
felt very happy.  And so we
also came across these three showrooms in Pendurthi.
My brother-in-law told us to go shopping for the shoot we wanted,
but they
kept going back and forth, saying the floor was fine.  After the shopping was complete, we headed
out.  Gaius filled
half the car with those bags
.  So that's all,
subscribe and see you again, boy.